



Piyali Sarkar Piyali Sarkar Reatured Featured System Developer seeking roles in Software Development, Application Development, Business Requirement Analysis, Project Management, IT Program Management, Requirement Gathering, Bug Fixing, Coding, Debugging, MySQL, Codeigniter, PHP, Javascript, JQuery, Ajax, CSS... Current Designation: Senior System Developer Total Experience: 6 Year(s) 0 Month(s) Current Company: SODEXO TECHNICAL SERVICES INDIA Notice Period: 1 Month PVT. LTD Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computers] Current Location: Mumbai Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore.Mumbai.Pune Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming / Maintenance Role: Team Lead/Tech Lead Industry: IT-Software/Software Services Marital Status: Married Key Skills: System Developer, Team Lead/Tech Lead, Software Development, Application Development, Business Requirement Analysis, Project Management, IT Program Management, Requirement Gathering, Bug Fixing, Coding, Debugging, MySQL, Codeigniter, PHP, Javascript, JQuery, Ajax Verified : Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 22-Jan-21

1 Last Modified: 18-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

#### Summary

6 Years of dedicated industry experience as PHP and application software development. Currently leading 'HR portal' system .Ability to work both independently or as part of team. Knowledge of API Integration. Experience in Creating REST API's (Backend) for all platform (IOS AND ANDROID). Experience in integrating Firebase web and Mobile push Notification. Skills of Debugging errors. Highly Flexible and holding capabilities of learning New Technologies, Tools and Applications.

### Work Experience

SODEXO TECHNICAL SERVICES INDIA PVT. LTD as Senior System Developer May 2019 to Till Date

Project Name: ACCESSHR (Sodexo Internal HR Portal)

Client: Sodexo

URL: https://hrconnect.in.sodexonet.com/accesshr

ACCESSHR is an easy-to-use web based tool to manage all employee details, employee attendance, employee appraisal, internal jobs etc.

VARA UNITED PVT LIMITED as Senior Associate

Sep 2018 to May 2019

Project Name: VAMT Client: ICICI BANK

URL: http://vamt.icicibank.com/vamt

VAMT is an easy-to-use web based tool to manage all assets and license effectively where in it provides overview of all users and assigned to them with complete ,henceforth a base database for tracking company asset records. VAMT enables you to successfully store, manage and share all IT organizational assets inventory management data in most efficient way possible with staff, organization and clients.

#### Responsibility

- \* Communicating with client for any changes.
- \* Changes in New Requirement and Bug Fixing.

# SHORT FORMATS DIGITAL WORK PVT LIMITED as Software Developer

Sep 2017 to Jul 2018

Project Name: IDEA Phone Secure Client: IDEA

# 1

### **Important**

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld. Idea Phone Secure is a device security solution offered for idea users in India. Idea Phone Secure brings to you the next level of security and device ownership experience with features like:

Device Security against accidental damages to protect your phone from unforeseen incidents.

Transparent and seamless claim management process right within the App.

Real time status update during service request.

Diagnosis your phone for issues in performance of screen, camera, connectivity and sensors etc.

#### Responsibility.

- \* Created REST API's for all platform [iOS, Android]
- \* Involved in Backend coding required for Website.
- \* Defined Proper API documentation
- \* Understanding of business requirement document and functional specifications.

#### SHORT FORMATS DIGITAL WORK PVT LIMITED (Continued)

Project Name: Biscootsecure Store

Client: Shotfrormats

URL: http://store.biscootsecure.com/

BISCOOT SECURITY SOLUTIONS (BSS) an app which provide smart protection for your smart phone. BSS comes with Anitvirus products which protect your Smart device online with latest protection technology. BSS also comes with anti-theft features, which enables you to track and locate your lost phone, remotely you can lock your phone or erase data. BSS also have a Secure

Mobile backup feature to secure your contact list on email or external memory device.

BSS also provides a complimentary Insurance to the device against accidental damage, water damage and fire damage. Complimentary Insurance is by NEW India Assurance Company Limited.

#### Responsibility.

- Understanding of business requirement document and functional specifications.
- \* Created REST API's for all platform [iOS, Android]
- Final code deployment on server.

#### SHORT FORMATS DIGITAL WORK PVT LIMITED (Continued)

Project Name: BAAR.IN Client: Shotformats

URL: http://baar.in/admin/backoffice/

This was an insurance Portal

#### Responsibility:

- \* Site Maintenance and Bug Fixing...
- \* Worked on Client's New requirement

^ Back to Top

#### **Education**

### UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from Heritage Institute of Technology, Kolkata in 2010

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs: Diploma in COMPUTER SCIENCE

^ Back to Top

#### IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
PHP	7.4.8	2020	6 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
MySQL	5.6.19	2020	4 Year(s)
HTML5			
OBJECT ORIENTED PROGRAMMING			
css, javascript			
CODEIGNITER	3.1.9	2019	3 Year(s)
JQuery, Angular JS			
AJAX			
SVN			
REST API			
Windows 8/10, Linux			
GIT			

^ Back to Top

# Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak	

English	Proficient	✓	✓	✓
Hindi	Expert	✓		✓

^ Back to Top

# **Affirmative Action**

# **Work Authorization**

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent
Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQs - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.